downloadthat.com 2004-12-04

# tePlanet: Privacy Statement

**

Privacy Statement of tePlanet

**

**

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**

**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like tePlanet . We are based in US .  Our principal activity is:  Internet Based Services  Our privacy policy covers tePlanet and its Web sites: 

** Organisation Name:  |  tePlanet   
---|---  
Address:  |  P.O. Box 1475   
City, Zip:  |  Green Bay  ,  54305   
State:  |  WI   
Country:  |  US   
Controller:  |  tePlanet   
Web Sites(s):  |  http://www.teplanet.com   
**

**

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

**

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data. 

**

**** ** The services and links of our Web sites  **

**

Our Web sites enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Web sites do not include links to third party Web service providers. 

**

Automatic Collection of Information 

**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Web site 
  * Customer administration 

**

Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes: 

  * by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 
  * by sending an email ( support@teplanet.com ) 

**

Children's Privacy 

**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by: 

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child's personal data 

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personnal data from children on our Web site. 

**

Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

**

We disclose our visitors' personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations. 

Where we disclose your personal data for the same purposes as those indicated in the table below, we provide you with the means to  opt-out of disclosure: 

  * by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 
  * by sending an email ( support@teplanet.com ) 

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the table mentioned above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure: 

  * by sending an email ( support@teplanet.com ) 

**

Confidentiality / Security 

**

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data: 

  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password) 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorised modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**

Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

**

You can ask us, by: 

  * sending an email ( support@teplanet.com ) 

whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate by: 

  * sending an email ( support@teplanet.com ) 

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you,  within a week.  \- although we may before require proof of your identity -.  We will provide the information  without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased 
  * rectified or amended 
  * completed 

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data,  but will give reasons for our refusal. 

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

**

Privacy Compliance 

**

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy  instrument,  we are: 

  * voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure 

####  Self Assessment procedure 

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service  |  Customer Support   
---|---  
URL  |  http://www.teplanet.com   
Address  |  P.O. Box 1475 Green Bay, WI 54305   
Country  |  US   

####  Primary personal data/Business information 

**x** |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Other personal details and profiling data 

\-  |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Identifiers 

**x** |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Specific Data 

\-  |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
* * *

* * *
